star health ipo latest gmp as all eyes
on shares listing star health ipo's
share allotment has been finalized and
now all eyes are set on its shares
listing which is likely to be on friday
december 10. meanwhile the private
health insurer has cut its offer for
sale size to 400 indian rupees crore
from
5249 indian rupees crore after its
initial public offering got a tepid
response the ipo of the country's
largest private health insurance firm
was subscribed just 79 backed by
billionaire stock investor rakesh
gingenvilla the company had priced its
ipo between 870 to 900 indian rupees per
share safecrop investments india llp
will now sell 29.85 million shares and
not 30.68 million shares earlier planned
as per market observers star health
shares were quoting at a discount of 70
indian rupees in the gray market from
its issue price of 900 indian rupees a
share star health leading private health
insurer in the country is owned by a
consortium of investors like westbridge
capital and rakesh gingenville stay
connected and informed with mint
download our app now